worldwideinterweb.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy

**Team Party Worldwide LLC Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers all of the Team Party Worldwide LLC websites. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Ownership of Information**  
Team Party Worldwide LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on the Team Party Worldwide LLC websites.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Team Party Worldwide LLC. websites, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Team Party Worldwide LLC does not endorse these comments as they are opinions of users not associated with Team Party Worldwide LLC or it’s employees.

**Mailing List**  
Team Party Worldwide LLC may launch a mailing list for some or all of the Team Party Worldwide LLC websites. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Team Party Worldwide LLC has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Resignation Media LLC. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Team Party Worldwide LLC may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the Team Party Worldwide LLC websites.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Team Party Worldwide LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
The Team Party Worldwide LLC websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Resignation Media LLC. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Resignation Media LLC

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Team Party Worldwide LLC changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

**Copyright Information**  
All images on worldwideinterweb.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)  
If you believe that any content appearing on worldwideinterweb.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-Mail [wwinterweb@gmail.com](mailto:wwinterweb@gmail.com)  
following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.  
(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf  
Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
